A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, Field Offices, Paris, RG 6, SG 1 FA395
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Post-war, 1945-1959; 2; 81 Boxes; 42 cubic feet
  - Post-war - Correspondence, 01
    - DMPH Holland, 1948-1957 (Box 42, Folder 390)
      Julius, Henri Willem - (travel, public health) - 1951-1952 Van Kampen, R.J. - (clinical chemistry) - 1952 Kassenwaar, Anton - (fellowship, medical biochemistry) - 1954-1957 Keiser, D.P.R. - (pediatrics) - 1948, 1952
    - DMPH Holland - Leiden Institute of Preventive Medicine and School of Public Health, 1948-1951 (Box 43, Folder 391)
    - DMPH Holland - Leiden Institute of Preventive Medicine and School of Public Health, 1952-1956 (Box 43, Folder 392)
    - DMPH Holland, 1951-1956 (Box 43, Folder 393)
      Larentz de Haas, Albert Marie - (fellowship, neurology) - 1951-1956 Moll, J. - (anatomy) - 1953
    - DMPH Holland - Querido, Andries - (fellowship, internal medicine), 1948-1958 (Box 43, Folder 394)
    - DMPH Holland - Querido, Arie - (travel, mental hygiene), 1946-1955 (Box 43, Folder 395)
    - DMPH Holland - Research Committee for Sanitary Engineering, 1947-1954 (Box 43, Folder 396)
    - DMPH Holland - Research Committee for Sanitary Engineering - Documents (7), 1954-1959 (Box 43, Folder 397)
    - DMPH Holland - Sanitary Engineering, 1946-1955 (Box 43, Folder 398)
    - DMPH Holland - Utrecht University, 1940-1958 (Box 43, Folder 399)
      Faculty of Medicine - 1946-1958 Psychiatric Clinic - 1940, 1947, 1953
    - DMPH Holland - Utrecht University - Institute for Industrial Psychology, 1948-1957 (Box 43, Folder 400)
    - DMPH India - Chatterjee, Sailendra Kumar - (fellowship, anesthesiology), 1952-1953 (Box 43, Folder 401)
    - DMPH India, 1952-1954 (Box 44, Folder 402)
      Johnson, Lillian - (nursing) - 1952-1954 Misra, S.C. - (surgery) - 1953
    - DMPH India - Nursing, 1947-1953 (Box 44, Folder 403)
    - DMPH India - Paintal, Autar Singh - (fellowship, neurophysiology), 1950-1953 (Box 44, Folder 404)
    - DMPH India, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 405)
      Subrahmanyan, D.V. - (fellowship, sanitary engineering) - 1953 Weddell's Survey - (leprosy) - 1953
    - DMPH Iran - Nursing, 1947-1954 (Box 44, Folder 406)
    - DMPH Ireland - Declinations, 1953-1954 (Box 44, Folder 407)
      Clarke, Noel - (pathology) - 1954 Cannon, Paul - (clinical physiology and cardiology) - 1953 Hegarty, Michael - (undergraduate medicine) - 1953
    - DMPH Ireland, 1947-1957 (Box 44, Folder 408)
      Dundon, Sheamus - (declination, pediatrics) - 1947-1953 Jessop, W.E. - (declination, physiology) - 1953-1957 Ministry of Health - 1949-1953
    - DMPH Ireland - Miscellaneous, 1954-1955 (Box 44, Folder 409)
      Fletcher, Evan - (declination, cardiology) - 1955 Godden, W.G. - (civil engineering) - 1954
    - DMPH Ireland - National University of Ireland - University College, London - Medical Faculty, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 410)
    - DMPH Israel - Jerusalem - (general correspondence), 1948-1958 (Box 44, Folder 411)
    - DMPH Israel - Jerusalem - Report - "The Health Services of Israel", 1952 (Box 44, Folder 412)
    - DMPH Israel - Sachs, Leo - (human genetics), 1954 (Box 44, Folder 413)
    - DMPH Italy, 1948-1956 (Box 44, Folder 414)
      Alella, Alfredo - (fellowship, physiology) - 1950-1955 Alessandrini, Maria - (travel, chemistry) - 1948-1953 Alduini, Arnaldo - (fellowship, physiology) - 1948-1956
    - DMPH Italy, 1951-1954 (Box 44, Folder 415)
      Bari University - Institute of Clinical Medicine - 1952-1954 Cambi, Franco - (travel, sanitary engineering) - 1951-1954 Carr, Nicolo - (sanitary engineering) - 1951-1953
    - DMPH Italy - Cappelini, Ruggero - (fellowship, genetics and serology), 1954-1958 (Box 45, Folder 416)
    - DMPH Italy, 1951-1953 (Box 45, Folder 417)
      Cernuto, Paolo - (sanitary engineering) - 1952 Checcia, Carlo - (declination, internal medicine) - 1952-1953 Cirri, Sergio B. - (anatomy) - 1951
    - DMPH Italy - Declinations, 1952-1955 (Box 45, Folder 418)
      Davini, Anna Maria - (pediatrics) - 1954 Floris, Vincenzo - (neuropsychiatry) - 1954 Jacono, Gustavo - (experimental psychology) - 1953-1954 Jannaconne, Angelo - (endocrinology) - 1953-1955 Marandola, Guiseppi - (neurosurgery) - 1952-1954 Pavia University - Institute of Medical Pathology - (equipment) - 1954 Pirodda, Ettore - (equipment, ear, nose, throat clinic) - 1954 Ricci, Marcello - (helminthology) - 1952-1954 Sereni, Fabio - (pediatrics, equipment) - 1954-1955 Vigliani, Enrico C. - (industrial hygiene) - 1954 Zanghi, Mariano - (electro-physiology) - 1954
    - DMPH Italy, 1948-1952 (Box 45, Folder 419)
      Dogo, G. - (surgery) - 1948 di Ferrante, Nicholi - (declination, endocrinology) - 1952
    - DMPH Italy - Fidanza, Flaminio - (fellowship, physiology), 1952-1953 (Box 45, Folder 420)
    - DMPH Italy - Florence University - Faculty of Medicine, 1947-1952 (Box 45, Folder 421)
    - DMPH Italy - Florence University - Institute of Experimental Psychology, 1951-1958 (Box 45, Folder 422)
    - DMPH Italy - Florence University - Institute of Experimental Psychology - Documents (5), 1953-1958 (Box 46, Folder 423)
    - DMPH Italy - Florence University, 1948-1955 (Box 47, Folder 424)
      Institute of Pharmacology - 1948-1955 Pediatric Clinic - 1948-1955
    - DMPH Italy - Fly Study, 1950-1956 (Box 47, Folder 425)
    - DMPH Italy - Fly Study, 1950-1956 (Box 47, Folder 426)
    - DMPH Italy, 1950-1954 (Box 47, Folder 427)
      Frighi, Luigi - (fellowship, psychiatry) - 1950-1954 Malandra, Bruno - (declination, pathology) - 1953-1954 Marotta, Domenico - (travel, public health) - 1951-1954 Medical Care - 1952-1953
    - DMPH Italy - Milan University, 1945-1958 (Box 47, Folder 428)
      Clinic for Nervous and Mental Diseases - 1948, 1951-1954 Faculty of Medicine - 1954 Institute of Hygiene - 1945, 1948-1955 Institute of Physiology - 1947-1958
    - DMPH Italy - Miscellaneous, 1953-1955 (Box 47, Folder 429)
      Lombardi, Benito - (medical biology) - 1955 Oppi, Raffaele - (request for information) - 1954 Peyton, Mary F. - (public health) - 1953-1954 Ricci, Gianfranco - (neurophysiology) - 1954-1955 Scanu, Angelo - (internal medicine) - 1955
    - DMPH Italy - Montagnani, Carlo A. - (surgery), 1950-1954 (Box 47, Folder 430)
    - DMPH Italy - Naples University, 1952-1955 (Box 47, Folder 431)
      Faculty of Medicine - 1954-1955 Department of Biological Chemistry - 1952-1954
    - DMPH Italy - Naples University - Department of Engineering, 1949-1956 (Box 47, Folder 432)
    - DMPH Italy - Naples University - Institute of Genetics, 1950-1955 (Box 48, Folder 433)
    - DMPH Italy - Naples University - Institute of Genetics - Supplementary Material, 1950-1954; 9 items (Box 48, Folder 434)
    - DMPH Italy, 1952-1955 (Box 48, Folder 435)
      Nursing - 1952-1954 Padua University - Faculty of Medicine - 1955
    - DMPH Italy - Pavia University, 1951-1955 (Box 48, Folder 436)
      Faculty of Medicine - 1955 Laboratory of Human Genetics - (proposed) - 1951-1952
    - DMPH Italy - Pavia University - Center of Genetics, 1948-1956 (Box 48, Folder 437)
    - DMPH Italy - Pavia University - Center of Genetics, 1948-1956 (Box 48, Folder 438)
    - DMPH Italy - Pavia University - Center of Genetics - Supplementary Material, 1953-1955; 7 items (Box 48, Folder 439)
    - DMPH Italy - Pisa University - Department of Physiology, 1951-1958 (Box 48, Folder 440)
    - DMPH Italy - Pisa University - Department of Physiology, 1951-1958 (Box 48, Folder 441)
    - DMPH Italy - Rome Institute of Hygiene - Virus Laboratory, 1951-1956 (Box 49, Folder 442)
    - DMPH Italy - Rome School of Public Health - (proposed), 1952-1954 (Box 49, Folder 443)
    - DMPH Italy, 1947-1955 (Box 49, Folder 444)
      Rome University - Faculty of Medicine - 1952-1955 Ruffilli, Domenico - (declination, virus research) - 1952 Sanitary Engineering - 1954 Spaccarelli, George - (declination, neurophysiology) - 1949-1954 Turin University - Faculty of Medicine - 1947-1954
    - DMPH Italy - Wirth, Alberto - (fellowship, neurophysiology), 1951-1956 (Box 49, Folder 445)
    - DMPH Italy - Zanchetti, Alberto - (fellowship, physiology), 1948-1955 (Box 49, Folder 446)
    - DMPH Norway - Abrahamsen, Ruth Mathilde - (fellowship, nursing), 1952-1954 (Box 49, Folder 447)
    - DMPH Norway - Declinations, 1954 (Box 49, Folder 448)
      Garegg, S. - (public health administration) - 1954 Togerson, Olav - (pathology) - 1954
    - DMPH Norway, 1945-1955 (Box 49, Folder 449)
      Engedal, Knut - (travel, public health administration) - 1949-1952 Friestad, Oystein - (virology) - 1952-1953 Marthinsen, Arne - (fellowship, social medicine) - 1953-1955 Ministry of Health - 1945-1955 Miscellaneous - Eek, Sigurd - (radiology) - 1953
    - DMPH Norway - Nursing, 1951-1958 (Box 49, Folder 450)
    - DMPH Norway - Oslo University - Department of Anatomy, 1934, 1937, 1945, 1947-1957 (Box 49, Folder 451)
    - DMPH Norway - Oslo University - Department of Psychiatry, 1937, 1939, 1945-1950 (Box 49, Folder 452)
    - DMPH Norway - Oslo University - Department of Psychiatry, 1951-1957 (Box 50, Folder 453)
    - DMPH Norway - Oslo University - Department of Psychiatry - Reprints (8), 1950-1956 (Box 50, Folder 454)
    - DMPH Norway - Oslo University - Laboratory of Respiratory Physiology, 1948-1957 (Box 50, Folder 455)
    - DMPH Norway - Oslo University - Laboratory of Respiratory Physiology - Reports (3), 1952-1957 (Box 50, Folder 456)
    - DMPH Norway, 1948-1958 (Box 50, Folder 457)
      Rorstad, Gunnvor - (fellowship, nursing) - 1954-1956 Seip, Martin Frederick - (travel, pediatrics) - 1950-1954 Sem-Jacobsen, Carl Wilhelm - (travel, psychiatry) - 1951-1958 Spilling, Ragnhild - (fellowship, nursing) - 1948-1953
    - DMPH Norway - Ulleval Hospital, 1950-1957 (Box 50, Folder 458)
      Endocrine Laboratory - 1954-1955 University Institute of Experimental Medical Research - 1950-1957
    - DMPH Norway, 1950-1956 (Box 50, Folder 459)
      Welle-Strand, Kirsten - (fellowship, nursing) - 1950-1954 Wergeland, Hjalmar - (fellowship, child psychiatry) - 1954-1956 Woien, Per Reidar - (fellowship, public health) - 1953-1955
    - DMPH Pakistan, 1952-1955 (Box 50, Folder 460)
      Begum, Khurshid - (fellowship, anesthesiology) - 1952-1954 Ullah, Inayat - (fellowship, internal medicine) - 1952-1955
    - DMPH Poland - Wissotsky-Krynski, Ida - (nursing), 1952-1953 (Box 50, Folder 461)
    - DMPH Portugal, 1948-1954 (Box 51, Folder 462)
      Bachmann de Mello, Margarida - (fellowship, nursing) - 1951-1953 Colaco, Amedeu F. - (public health and tropical medicine) - 1948-1953 Gentil da Silva Martins, Alice - (fellowship, nursing) - 1953-1954
    - DMPH Portugal - Lisbon Institute of Tropical Medicine, 1944-1954 (Box 51, Folder 463)
    - DMPH Portugal - Lisbon School of Nursing, 1948-1957 (Box 51, Folder 464)
    - DMPH Portugal - Moura, Amilcar - (fellowship, psychological medicine), 1952-1953 (Box 51, Folder 465)
    - DMPH Portugal, 1951-1954 (Box 51, Folder 466)
      Nursing - 1951-1954 Moniz Pereira, Maria Jose Gomes - (fellowship, nursing) - 1952-1953 Ramos dos Santos, Maria da Lourdes - (fellowship, nursing) - 1953-1954 Regala, Crisanta - (fellowship, nursing) - 1951-1954
    - DMPH Scotland - Baird, Dugald - (obstetrics), 1949-1957 (Box 51, Folder 467)
    - DMPH Scotland, 1949-1955 (Box 51, Folder 468)
      Carter, Gladys - (nursing) - 1949-1955 Cookson, Joyce - (fellowship, psychology) - 1953-1955
    - DMPH Scotland - Dundee Medical School, 1951-1958 (Box 51, Folder 469)
    - DMPH Scotland - Dundee Medical School - Social Medicine Teaching Project, 1955-1956 (Box 52, Folder 470)
    - DMPH Scotland - Edinburgh University, 1947-1956 (Box 52, Folder 471)
      Faculty of Medicine - 1947, 1951-1956 Department of Pharmacology - 1949-1955 Department of Physiology - 1951-1955 Department of Psychology - 1947-1956 Department of Public Health and Social Medicine - 1947-1956
    - DMPH Scotland - Edinburgh University - Teaching General Practice, 1949-1958 (Box 52, Folder 472)
    - DMPH Scotland - Edinburgh University - Teaching General Practice, 1949-1958 (Box 52, Folder 473)
    - DMPH Scotland - Edinburgh University - Teaching General Practice - Documents (6), 1952-1957 (Box 52, Folder 474)
    - DMPH Scotland - Glasgow University, 1948-1955 (Box 52, Folder 475)
      Faculty of Medicine - 1948-1955 Department of Biochemistry - 1953-1955 Department of Materia Medica and Therapeutics - 1950-1954
    - DMPH Scotland - Illingworth, C.F.W. - (travel, surgery), 1953 (Box 53, Folder 476)
    - DMPH Scotland - Lamb, Margaret C.W. - (fellowship, nursing), 1950-1954 (Box 53, Folder 477)
    - DMPH Scotland, 1937-1955 (Box 53, Folder 478)
      Macarthur, John Gordon - (declination, cardiology) - 1950-1952 Methven, Margaret - (travel, pediatrics) - 1951-1953 Miekeljohn, A. Peter - (nutrition, medicine) - 1948-1955 Millar, Malcolm - (travel, psychosomatic medicine) - 1937, 1951-1954
    - DMPH Scotland, 1951-1955 (Box 53, Folder 479)
      Ministry of Health - 1951-1955 Nursing - 1951-1954 Royal Hospital for Sick Children - Child Guidance Clinic - 1951-1954
    - DMPH Scotland, 1949-1956 (Box 53, Folder 480)
      Royal Technical College - Environmental Control Engineering - 1954-1955 Scott, Richard - (travel, public health) - 1951-1952 Swann, Margaret Blythe - (travel, psychiatric social work) - 1953-1954 Thompson, Angus M. - (social medicine) - 1949-1953 Walker, James - (travel, obstetrics) - 1954-1956
    - DMPH South Africa, 1936-1956 (Box 53, Folder 481)
      Capetown University - Faculty of Medicine - 1936, 1938, 1939, 1948, 1950-1955 Cohn, Helen Dorothy - (travel, nursing) - 1952-1953 Johannesburg University of the Witwatersrand - Faculty of Medicine - 1949-1956 Natal University - Durban Medical School - 1949-1955 Wright, James Westland - (fellowship, sanitary engineering) - 1953-1955
    - DMPH Spain - Barcelona University - Faculty of Medicine, 1947-1953 (Box 53, Folder 482)
    - DMPH Spain - Declinations, 1951-1955 (Box 53, Folder 483)
      Bofill Tuarer, P. - (psychiatry) - 1952-1954 Carrell Institute of Medical Research - 1954 Children's Hospital, Salamanca - 1955 Corominar Beret, Frederic - (neuropediatrics) - 1955 Gibert-Queralto, Juan - (cardiology) - 1953-1954 Ribas Mujal, Diego - (histology) - 1954 Otero Soto, Juan - (gynecology) - 1952 Paravissini Para, Jose - (cardiology) - 1953 Verdaquer, F. - (respiratory diseases) - 1951-1952
    - DMPH Spain - Kapff, Jutta - (declination, pharmacology), 1953 (Box 53, Folder 484)
    - DMPH Spain - Larramendi, Luis Manuel Hernando - (fellowship, neurophysiology), 1948-1956 (Box 54, Folder 485)
    - DMPH Spain - Ley Garcia, Adolfo - (neurosurgery), 1947-1956 (Box 54, Folder 486)
    - DMPH Spain - Miscellaneous, 1936-1955 (Box 54, Folder 487)
      Bravo, Julio - (public health) - 1952-1953 Llado, Nuri - (psychology) - 1936, 1949-1952 Martinez Caro, Diego - (experimental surgery) - 1954-1955 Russell, Paul F. - Memo Regarding DMPH Cooperation in Spain - 1952 Soler-Bachs, Jorges - (electro-physiology) - 1953
    - DMPH Spain - Nursing, 1946-1954 (Box 54, Folder 488)
    - DMPH Spain - Sarro-Burbano, Ramon - (travel, psychiatry), 1949-1955 (Box 54, Folder 489)
    - DMPH Spain - Segarra-Obiol, Jose Manuel - (fellowship, neurology), 1948, 1950-1956 (Box 54, Folder 490)
    - DMPH Sweden, 1950-1957 (Box 54, Folder 491)
      Akerlindh, Gunnar - (sanitary engineering) - 1950-1954 Andersson, Bengt - (fellowship, physiology) - 1950-1957 Assarsson, Stig - (declination, public health) - 1951 Bergman, Bengt Arne - (declination, public health) - 1951-1952 Carstensen, Hans - (declination, physiology) - 1954-1955
    - DMPH Sweden - Cederstrom, Hjalmar - (hospital architecture), 1948-1953 (Box 54, Folder 492)
    - DMPH Sweden - Pahlstrom, Greta - (travel, nursing), 1952-1954 (Box 54, Folder 493)
    - DMPH Sweden - Declinations, 1951-1954 (Box 55, Folder 494)
      Akerren, Bo and Kjellander, Jan - (public health) - 1954 Ellasch, Harold - (internal medicine) - 1952-1953 Hagbaith, K.E. - (neurophysiology) - 1952 Kjellander, Borje - (public health) - 1951
    - DMPH Sweden, 1946-1956 (Box 55, Folder 495)
      Fischer, Gunnar - (travel, public health) - 1946-1956 Folkow, Bjorn - (fellowship, physiology) - 1952-1954 Friberg, Lars Torsten - (travel, occupational health) - 1951-1952 Fries, Por Eric - (psychiatry) - 1951-1952
    - DMPH Sweden - Granit, Rangar - (neurophysiology), 1940, 1946-1957 (Box 55, Folder 496)
    - DMPH Sweden, 1945-1955 (Box 55, Folder 497)
      Goteborg School of Nursing - 1948-1954 Gothenburg University - Psychotechnical Institute - 1945-1954 Hedlund, Sven - (fellowship, cardiology) - 1951-1955
    - DMPH Sweden - Hokfeldt, Bernt - (fellowship, endocrinology), 1952-1956 (Box 55, Folder 498)
    - DMPH Sweden, 1950-1954 (Box 55, Folder 499)
      Hood, Bertil - (declination, renal physiology) - 1950-1954 Ivemark, Bjorn - (fellowship, pediatrics) - 1952-1954 Janson, Karin - (fellowship, nursing) - 1950-1954
    - DMPH Sweden - Kallen, Bengt - (fellowship, embryology), 1952-1954 (Box 55, Folder 500)
      Hood, Bertil - (declination, renal physiology) - 1950-1954
    - DMPH Sweden - Karolinska Institute - Laboratory of Experimental Surgery, 1949-1955 (Box 55, Folder 501)
    - DMPH Sweden - Karolinska Institute - Pediatric Clinic, 1947-1955 (Box 55, Folder 502)
    - DMPH Sweden, 1946-1954 (Box 56, Folder 503)
      Harlberg, Petter Jonas Erik - (fellowship, pediatrics) - 1947-1953 Kugelberg, Eric Klaus - (travel, neurology) - 1946, 1949-1954
    - DMPH Sweden - Landgren, Sven Olof Esbjorn - (fellowship, physiology), 1950-1956 (Box 56, Folder 504)
    - DMPH Sweden - Liljestrand, Ake - (fellowship, physiology), 1953-1956 (Box 56, Folder 505)
    - DMPH Sweden, 1950-1953 (Box 56, Folder 506)
      Linder, Lars - (declination, public health) - 1951-1952 Lindgren, Inga - (fellowship, physiology) - 1950-1953
    - DMPH Sweden - Lund University - Department of Clinical Chemistry, 1953-1956 (Box 56, Folder 507)
    - DMPH Sweden - Lund University - Institute of Physiology, 1950, 1952-1956 (Box 56, Folder 508)
    - DMPH Sweden - Lund University - Laboratory of Mycology, 1951-1954 (Box 56, Folder 509)
    - DMPH Sweden - Lund University Hospital - Department of Internal Medicine, 1946, 1948-1957 (Box 56, Folder 510)
    - DMPH Sweden, 1950-1956 (Box 56, Folder 511)
      Lundblad, Marta - (fellowship, nursing) - 1952-1954 Malmo Medical Clinic - 1950-1956
    - DMPH Sweden - Miscellaneous, 1951-1955 (Box 56, Folder 512)
      Paletius, K. - (neurosurgery) - 1951 Edlund, Torbjorn - (pharmacology) - 1952 Gerhardsson, Gideon - (industrial hygiene) - 1954-1955 Hellstrom, Bo - (ophthalmology) - 1954
    - DMPH Sweden - Nursing, 1952-1955 (Box 56, Folder 513)
    - DMPH Sweden - Odeblad, Eric - (fellowship, autoradiography), 1952-1956 (Box 57, Folder 514)
    - DMPH Sweden - Odeblad, Eric - (fellowship, autoradiography) - Supplementary Material, 1949-1951; 22 items (Box 57, Folder 515)
    - DMPH Sweden, 1949-1955 (Box 57, Folder 516)
      Ohlin, Inga Britta Linnea - (fellowship, nursing) - 1950-1954 St. Eric's Hospital, Stockholm - 1949-1953 St. George's Hospital, Stockholm - 1955 Smith, Gudmund - (fellowship, psychology) - 1951-1954
    - DMPH Sweden, 1947-1954 (Box 57, Folder 517)
      Stockholm Institute of Public Health - 1951-1954 Stockholm Veterinary High School - Institute of Physiology - 1948-1953 Svaetichin, Gunnar - (travel, physiology) - 1949-1952 Thesleff, Stephen - (fellowship, pharmacology) - 1951-1953 Umea School of Nursing - 1947-1953
    - DMPH Switzerland - Basel University, 1947-1956 (Box 57, Folder 518)
      Faculty of Medicine - 1947-1955 Institute of Hygiene and Bacteriology - 1951-1956
    - DMPH Switzerland - Bern University, 1945-1956 (Box 57, Folder 519)
      Institute of Pharmacology - 1953-1956 Institute of Physiology - 1945, 1947-1956
    - DMPH Switzerland, 1948-1954 (Box 57, Folder 520)
      Bersch, Marie Cecil - (fellowship, nursing) - 1948, 1951-1954 Biasch, Hans - (travel, industrial psychology) - 1952-1953 Dardel, Walter - (sanitary engineering) - 1950-1954
    - DMPH Switzerland - Declinations - Moor-Jankowski, J.K. - (genetics), 1955 (Box 57, Folder 521)
    - DMPH Switzerland, 1948-1955 (Box 57, Folder 522)
      Egli, Robert E. - (fellowship, industrial hygiene) - 1953-1955 Exchaquet, Nicole - (fellowship, nursing) - 1948, 1951-1954
    - DMPH Switzerland - Geneva University - Anatomical Laboratory, 1936, 1947-1955 (Box 58, Folder 523)
    - DMPH Switzerland - Geneva University - Institute of Human Genetics - Ophthalmological Clinic, 1949-1956 (Box 58, Folder 524)
    - DMPH Switzerland - Geneva University - Institute of Physiology, 1951-1955 (Box 58, Folder 525)
    - DMPH Switzerland - Geneva University - Institut des Sciences de l'Education, 1945-1955 (Box 58, Folder 526)
    - DMPH Switzerland - Gysler, Aurora - (fellowship, nursing), 1948-1955 (Box 58, Folder 527)
    - DMPH Switzerland, 1947-1954 (Box 58, Folder 528)
      Hallaver, D.C. - (declination, virology) - 1950-1954 Inhelder, Boubel - (travel, psychology) - 1947-1954
    - DMPH Switzerland - Le Bon Secours School of Nursing, 1951-1958 (Box 58, Folder 529)
    - DMPH Switzerland - Le Bon Secours School of Nursing, 1951-1958 (Box 58, Folder 530)
    - DMPH Switzerland - Le Bon Secours School of Nursing - Documents (3), 1955 (Box 58, Folder 531)
    - DMPH Switzerland - Miscellaneous, 1951-1955 (Box 58, Folder 532)
      Bangerter, A. - (ophthalmology) - 1952-1953 Dolivo, Michel - (neurophysiology) - 1954-1955 Siemsen, Jan - (internal medicine) - 1951-1953 Zehnder, Max A. - (former fellowship candidate, neurosurgery) - 1951
    - DMPH Switzerland, 1950-1956 (Box 59, Folder 533)
      Monnier, Eva - (nursing) - 1953 Muller, Edith - (fellowship, nursing) - 1953-1956 Nursing - 1953-1955 Pairs, Jean-Marie - (fellowship, nursing) - 1950-1954
    - DMPH Switzerland, 1947-1954 (Box 59, Folder 534)
      Paur, Anne-Marie - (fellowship, nursing) - 1952-1954 Pestalozzi Children's Village - 1947, 1953 Social Work - 1949-1954 Witt, Peter Nicolaus - (fellowship, pharmacology) - 1951-1953
    - DMPH Switzerland, 1950-1954 (Box 59, Folder 535)
      Zurich Federal Institute for Waters - 1952-1954 Zurich Technical High School - (public health engineering, industrial hygiene) - 1950-1954
    - DMPH Switzerland - Zurich University, 1937-1954 (Box 59, Folder 536)
      Faculty of Medicine - 1945-1954 Institute of Brain Antomy - 1939, 1947-1952 Institute of Physiology - 1937, 1947-1954
    - DMPH Switzerland - Zurich University - Psychiatric Clinic, 1933, 1935, 1937, 1940, 1948-1955 (Box 59, Folder 537)
    - DMPH Syria, 1945-1955 (Box 59, Folder 538)
      American University of Beirut - Faculty of Medicine - 1945-1954 Cornet, Francoise - (nursing) - 1953-1955 Miscellaneous - Berthet, Etienne - "Bilan d'une Annee d'Activities Antituberculeuses en Syrie" - June 1952-June 1953 Miscellaneous - Mahassen, Dr. - (thoracic surgery) - 1954
    - DMPH Turkey, 1947-1954 (Box 59, Folder 539)
      Ari, Azmi Bozkurt - (virology) - 1954 School of Public Health, Ankara - 1952 Nursing - 1947-1953
    - DMPH United States, 1952-1955 (Box 59, Folder 540)
      Adams, Raymond D. - (travel, neurology) - 1954 Adams, Wright - (travel, medicine) - 1954-1955 Brown, Esther Lucille - (public health) - 1952-1953
    - DMPH United States - Declinations, 1953-1954 (Box 59, Folder 541)
      Amdur, Mar - (biochemistry) - 1953-1954 Bromsky, Irving - (physiology) - 1954 Simons, H.C.R. - (multiple sclerosis) - 1953
    - DMPH United States, 1948-1956 (Box 60, Folder 542)
      Francis, Thomas - (travel, epidemiology) - 1953 Howard University - Faculty of Medicine - 1952-1955 Howard University - Department of Preventive Medicine - 1948-1956
    - DMPH United States - Hilleboe, Herman E. - (public health), 1947-1954 (Box 60, Folder 543)